<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICP Demo</string>
    <string name="version_string">version 1.0.0</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome To KiwiViewer</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Thanks for installing KiwiViewer!\n\nVisit us at www.kiwiviewer.org for more information.</string>

    <string name="copyright_text">\u00A9 2011 <a href='http://www.kitware.com'>Kitware, Inc.</a></string>
    <string name="license_link"><a href='http://kiwiviewer.org/kiwiviewer/project/parti.html'>Acknowledgements</a></string>

    <string name="brainatlas_title">SPL-PNL Brain Atlas</string>
    <string name="brainatlas_message">
The brain atlas is distributed under the Slicer license.  For more information please visit http://www.slicer.org/publications/item/view/1265\n\n
Interactions:\n\n
-single tap a model to hide it\n\n
-double tap a model to single it out\n\n
-long press anywhere to show all models again\n\n
-touch and drag the clip plane to move it\n\n
-touch and drag the handle to rotate the clip plane\n\n
-tap the top left corner of the screen to hide/show the clip plane\n\n
</string>

    <string name="can_title">Can Simulation</string>
    <string name="can_message">
This dataset contains 44 timesteps from a simulation of a block crushing a can.  The models are colored by velocity magnitude.\n\n
Interactions:\n\n
-touch Play to start the animation\n\n
-while animation is paused, touch and drag up/down on the left edge of the screen to advance the animation\n\n
-while animation is playing, touch and drag up/down on the left edge of the screen to adjust animation speed\n\n
</string>

    <string name="head_image_title">Head CT Image</string>
    <string name="head_image_message">
This dataset is a CT scan of a human head.  The image is displayed using three orthogonal slice planes.  An isosurface of the skull is computed on the fly and displayed as a translucent surface mesh.\n\n
Interactions:\n\n
-touch and drag a slice plane to move it\n\n
-double tap anywhere to toggle transparency of the skull\n\n
</string>

    <string name="external_data_url">http://www.kiwiviewer.org/data</string>
    <string name="cannot_open_asset_title">Sorry</string>
    <string name="cannot_open_asset_message">KiwiViewer for Android 2.2 is unable to open apk asset files greater than 1MB.  Instead, you can download the data from http://www.kiwiviewer.org/data and then open it in KiwiViewer.</string>


</resources>
